

CONTACT ME AT

- Dist & Tehsil Mardan (KP).
- syedaasimshah1@gmail.com
- http:///aasimshah.tk
- in @aasimshah

SKILLS SUMMARY

- •••• Project Management
- • • Full stack DEvelopment (PHP)
- ●●●● PHP development & fixing
- • • Front _ End Development
- •••• Team Leading
- •••• HTMl, Css, JavaScript, jQuery, Ajax-call, PHP, laravel, mysql

MY PROJECTS

- www.specscamp.com.
- weluv.link (project from fiverr)
- bestmenu.com (project from fiverr)

SYED ASIM SHAH

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER

PERSONAL PROFILE

This is Aasim shah from Pakistan, I am working as full stack web developer for more than 3 years on fiverr and other freelancing sites, having more than enough exp in Frontend as well as Logic building (Back_end) in PHP and laravel.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Freelancere

Fiverr and hire pre hour | Oct 2019 - present

- Conduct day-to-day project coordination, planning, and implementation across multiple teams
- create multi vender websites on my own with frontend and backend with MYsql Database.

Senior Front-End Designer

fiverr | Jan 2020 - present

- Managed complex projects from start to finish
- Collaborated with other designers
- Fully responsive and mobile friendly work, custom animations though pure Css and javascript, high-level designs.

EDUCATIONAL HISTORY

Aup Peshawar (Aggriculture University)

Bachelor's in Computer Science | oct 2019 - present

- Studied object oriented programing in javaScript , PHP and python.
- Studied project planning, coordination, and ethics
- Worked with various startups on launching new websites and providing services

Quaid E Azam collage

Fsc | mar 2017 - mar 2019

- Percentage: 78%
- This is one of the best collage in KP, have learned alot about teamwork, team managments and many more.